#### Contact

tiffany.n.dao@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/tiffany-dao-1b037760 (LinkedIn)

## Top Skills

**Operating Room** 

Nursing

**Pediatrics** 

### Certifications

Basic Life Support
Certified Nurse Operative Room
(CNOR)

# Tiffany Dao

Clinical Nurse Coordinator at Texas Children's Hospital Houston, Texas

# Summary

Experienced surgical nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Microsoft Word, healthcare, patient advocacy, patient safety, and adult as well as pediatric experience. Strong healthcare services professional in the process of obtaining a Master's degree focused in MHA/MBA from University of Houston-Clear Lake.

# Experience

Texas Children's Hospital Clinical Nurse Coordinator of the Cochlear Implant Program February 2020 - Present (4 months)

**Texas Medical Center** 

Houston Methodist RN III Operating Room BSN, RN, CNOR January 2014 - February 2020 (6 years 2 months)

Texas Medical Center

- Circulate adult general surgery cases
- Member of Liver Transplant Team
- •Liver Team Call Scheduler
- •Unit Co-Scheduler of 100 staff members
- LaborWorkx Project Write-Up
- Chair of Scheduling Shared Governance Committee
- •Quality and safety projects (Time-Out and Medication Administration Audits)
- •Clinical Content Build Out Subject Matter Expert for Liver Transplant Information in OpTime
- Liver Transplant Time-Out creator
- Maintain Liver Circulator Checklist for Liver Team Orientees
- Mock Circulating Class for new employees
- Count Policy Debrief for new employees
- Member of Operating Room Journal Club
- •Member of Hospital-wide Hemostasis Ad Hoc Committee
- Serve as mentor

·Serve as preceptor

Memorial Hermann Health System RN II Operating Room BSN, RN January 2011 - January 2014 (3 years 1 month)

**Texas Medical Center** 

- •Deliver quality care to patients according to the age and needs of the patient
- •Coordinate the planning for delivery of nursing care with a multidisciplinary team
- •Administer appropriate clinical decisions in the delivery of patient care
- •Serve as preceptor and resource
- •Educate operating room staff about malignant hyperthermia
- •Filmed Pediatric Surgical Safety Checklist Training Video for Children's Memorial Hermann
- Completed Clinical Coach Workshop
- •Participate in systemic, interdisciplinary, and ongoing evaluation committee for process improvement and desired client-centered outcomes
- •Experience in maternal-fetal, general, plastic, ENT, orthopedic, urology, dental, OMF, plastic, burns, and neurology surgeries

Texas Children's Hospital
Work Study - Patient Care Assistant
December 2009 - December 2010 (1 year 1 month)

**Texas Medical Center** 

- •Collect data from patient, family, lab, and other medical reports
- Complete nursing assessment of patient/family
- •Coordinate, analyze, synthesize, and document assessment information to determine patient needs and priorities of care
- •Develop plan of care and coordinate with other members of health care team
- Delegate specifics of care plan to unlicensed personnel
- Document patient responses to provided care
- Educate patients and families

#### Walgreens

Certified Pharmacy Technician October 2006 - September 2009 (3 years)

16185 Space Center Boulevard, Houston, TX 77062

- •Deliver quality patient care and customer service
- Input patient information
- Scan, input, fill, and sell prescriptions

- •Collaborate with physicians and pharmacists
- Maintain inventory

## Kumon Learning Center

**Assistant Manager** 

June 2001 - September 2006 (5 years 4 months)

- •Recruit, train, and direct employees
- Coordinate daily activities
- Collect and process tuition
- •Plan lessons
- Teach students
- Communicate with parents

# Education

University of Houston-Clear Lake

Master's degree, MHA/MBA · (2018 - 2022)

The University of Texas Health Science Center at Houston (UTHealth)

BSN, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2009 - 2010)

University of Houston

Nursing Pre-requisites · (2005 - 2008)

Clear Lake High School

· (2001 - 2005)